Finding Aid for University Productions poster collection, 1936-2012
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
University Productions poster collection 1936-2012, 1950-2012
University of Michigan. University Productions.
4 oversize folders
10 linear feet
92126 Bimu F65 2
Various posters advertising theatrical and musical productions put on by the University of Michigan School of Music, Theatre & Dance and related units ranging from 1936 to the present. Includes posters from the Department of Speech (before the School of Music had a separate theatre department). Dance Company, Department of Music, Department of Musical Theater, Department of Theater and Drama, and the Opera Theater program.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was donated by University Productions (Donor No. 7556 ) beginning in 1988.
Periodic additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open without restriction.
University Productions is the unit responsible for University of Michigan School of Music, Theatre & Dance productions. Productions include both professional productions and university productions in dance, theatre, opera, and musical theatre. The unit has been responsible for managing music and theatre facilities, including Hill Auditorium, Lydia Mendelssohn Theatre, Power Center for the Performing Arts, Rackham Auditorium, and Trueblood Theatre.
Earlier theatrical productions were done under the auspices of the Department of Speech which incorporated theatre before theatre and drama became a separate department after 1979.
The University Productions posters collection contains posters largely created by University Productions which handles music, dance, voice, and theatre productions for the University of Michigan School of Music, Theatre & Dance. The poster collection is arranged in eight series: Collage Concerts, Dance Company, Department of Music, Department of Musical Theater, Department of Speech, Department of Theater and Drama, Opera Theater and Oversize Files.
Subjects:
Subjects - Visual Materials:
University of Michigan--Dramatics.; University of Michigan. Professional Theatre Program.; University of Michigan. School of Music.; University of Michigan. Dept. of Speech.; Michigan Repertory Players.
Genre Terms:
Posters.
- Collage Concert 2007-2012
  Collage Concerts (0.1 linear feet, 2007-2012) are combined shows of theater, music, and dance.
  - 2007, 2009, 2010, 2012 (Box 1)
- Dance Company 1980-2012
  The Dance Company (0.5 linear feet, 1980-2012) series contains posters advertising the productions of the University Dance Company under the Department of Dance.
  - General 1980-1982 (Box 1)
  - Arcs in Time, 2009 (Box 1)
  - Carmina Burana, 1996 (Box 1)
  - The Choreography of Geography (Box 1)
  - Dance to the Music, 2006 (Box 1)
  - Dances of Passion, Rhythm and Heat, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Dancelucent, 2012 (Box 1)
  - Dancing Americas, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Dancing at 100, 2009 (Box 1)
  - Eurythmy: Visible Speech and Visible Song, 1957 (Box 1)
  - A Gallery of Dances (Box 1)
  - In the Spirit of Diaghilev, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Pulcinella (Box 1)
  - Revisionary Dances, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Rituals and Reveries, 2007 (Box 1)
  - Stravinsky Revisited, 2008 (Box 1)
  - Tanzmusik, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Trailblazers and Troubadours, 1991 (Box 1)
  - The Unicorn, the Gorgon and the Manticore (Box 1)
  - Vital Elements: Dances for 1990, 1990 (Box 1)
  - World Wide Rhythms, 2000 (Box 1)
- Department of Music 1955-2011
  The Department of Music (0.5 linear feet, 1955-2011, scattered) series contains posters from various concerts and programs including Symphonic Band concerts, Symphony and Philharmonia Orchestra concerts, Choir concerts, seminars, the Afro-American Music Collection, and general posters.
  - General 1961-1963, 1971, 1975, 1980, 1987 undated (Box 1)
  - Afro-American Music Collection 1978-1979, undated (Box 1)
  - Bands 1984-1986, 1988, 2000, 2007, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Choir undated (Box 1)
  - High School Seminars 1955, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
  - Symphony and Philharmonia Orchestra 1976, 2007-2008, 2010-2011, undated (Box 1)
- Department of Musical Theater 1999-2012
  The Department of Musical Theater (1.0 linear feet), 1999-2012) series contains posters for productions produced by the Department of Musical Theater in cooperation with the various music organizations of the university.
  - All's Well that Ends Well, 2010 (Box 2)
  - Big River, 2007 (Box 2)
  - The Boys from Syracuse, 2005 (Box 2)
  - Brigadoon, 1993, 2011 (Box 2)
  - Cabaret, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Carousel, 2008 (Box 2)
  - Chicago, 2012 (Box 2)
  - Company, 1991 (Box 2)
  - A Day in Hollywood, a Night in the Ukraine, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Die Fledermaus (Box 2)
  - Ella Minnow Pea, 2008 (Box 2)
  - Evita, 2009 (Box 2)
  - Forty-Second Street, 1995, 2009 (Box 2)
  - The Full Monty, 2011 (Box 2)
  - Gibson Fleck, 2010 (Box 2)
  - Grand Hotel, 1996 (Box 2)
  - If My Friends Could See Me Now, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Into the Woods, 1991, 2010 (Box 2)
  - A Little Night Music, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Little Women, 2011 (Box 2)
  - Love Life (Box 2)
  - The Most Happy Fella, 1994 (Box 2)
  - The Music Man, 1997 (Box 2)
  - The Mystery of Edwin Drood, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Of Thee I Sing, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Oh Coward!, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Our Country's Good, 2011 (Box 2)
  - Pajama Game, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Pal Joey, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Quilt, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Ragtime, 2010 (Box 2)
  - Rent, 2008 (Box 2)
  - Seussical, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Side Show, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Spring Awakening, 2012 (Box 2)
  - Sunday in the Park with George, 1994 (Box 2)
  - The Three Penny Opera, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Trafford Tanzi, 2009 (Box 2)
  - Twenty-fifth Anniversary Concert, 2009 (Box 2)
  - The Who's Tommy, 2007 (Box 2)
- Department of Speech 1936-1972
  The Department of Speech (3.0 linear feet, 1936-1972) series contains early posters from the Department before the School of Music divided into specific theatrical departments. The posters within include theater, musical theater, and opera.
  - Playbills, 1948-49 1951, 1955, 1957-1960 (Box 3)
  - Abe Lincoln and Illinois, 1949 (Box 3)
  - Amphitryon 38, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Arsenic and Old Lace, 1947, 1957 (Box 3)
  - As You Like It, 1960 (Box 3)
  - The Bartered Bride (Box 3)
  - The Beaux Stratagem, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Berkeley Square, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Caesar and Cleopatra, 1950 (Box 3)
  - The Clugstone Inheritance, 1955 (Box 3)
  - The Devil and Daniel Webster and Billy Budd (Box 3)
  - Desire Under the Elms, 1957 (Box 3)
  - Don Giovanni, 1952 (Box 3)
  - Dream Girl, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Epitaph for George Dillon, 1959 (Box 3)
  - The Fan, 1952 (Box 3)
  - The Good Woman of Setzuan, 1955 (Box 4)
  - Hansel and Gretel, 1956 (Box 4)
  - Inherit the Wind, 1958 (Box 4)
  - I Remember Mama, 1948 (Box 4)
  - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1948 (Box 4)
  - In Spite of Heaven, 1947 (Box 4)
  - Juno and the Paycock, 1956 (Box 4)
  - The Late George Apley, 1948 (Box 4)
  - Live on Air, 1951 (Box 4)
  - Look Homeward Angel, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Love's Labor's Lost, 1958 (Box 4)
  - The Magic Flute, 1951 (Box 4)
  - The Marriage of Figaro, 1947 (Box 4)
  - The Misanthrope, 1956 (Box 4)
  - My Very Own, 1956 (Box 4)
  - Of Thee I Sing, 1948 (Box 4)
  - Once in a Lifetime, 1952 (Box 4)
  - Potting Shed, 1958 (Box 4)
  - Playboy of the Western World, 1958 (Box 4)
  - A Philadelphia Story, 1958 (Box 4)
  - Papa is All, 1943 (Box 4)
  - Saint Joan, 1947 (Box 5)
  - The Taming of the Shrew, 1954 (Box 5)
  - There Shall Be No Night, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Under the Gaslight, 1956 (Box 5)
  - The Way of the World, 1960 (Box 5)
  - The Worlds of Tommy Albright, 1955 (Box 5)
  - You Can't Take it With You, 1936 (Box 5)
- Department of Theater and Drama 1946-2012
  The Department of Theater and Drama (4.0 linear feet, 1946-2012, scattered) series contains general posters from the department, as well as from specific sub groups, including the Ensemble Theater, the Michigan Repertory, the University Showcase, the Professional Theater Program, the University Players, the Musket, and Project Theater.
  - General
    - Playbills 1981-1982, undated (Box 6)
    - All the Way Home (Box 6)
    - Andromache, 1993 (Box 6)
    - Antigone (Box 6)
    - Arms and the Man, 2011 (Box 6)
    - As You Like It, 2008 (Box 6)
    - The Beaux' Stratagem, 2011 (Box 6)
    - The Birthday Party, 1992 (Box 6)
    - Bread and Roses, 1975 (Box 6)
    - The Burial at Thebes, 2006 (Box 6)
    - The Butterfingers Angel Mary and Joseph, Herod the Nut and the Slaughter of 12 Hit Carols in a Pear Tree (Box 6)
    - Catsplay (Box 6)
    - Cloud Nine, 2012 (Box 6)
    - The Collection (Box 6)
    - Colored People's Time, 2000 (Box 6)
    - The Cradle Will Rock, 2006 (Box 6)
    - The Crucible, 2011 (Box 6)
    - Dancing at Lughnasa (Box 6)
    - Dial M for Murder (Box 6)
    - Don't Bother Me, I Can't Cope, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Escape from Happiness, 1999 (Box 6)
    - A Flea in Her Ear, 2005 (Box 6)
    - Getting Out (Box 6)
    - Ghosts (Box 6)
    - The Glass Menagerie (Box 6)
    - The Gold Diggers, 2006 (Box 6)
    - Goodbye, My Fancy, 1952 (Box 6)
    - The Heidi Chronicles (Box 6)
    - Henry V (Box 6)
    - The House of Bernarda Alba (Box 6)
    - I Am a Man (Box 6)
    - I Can't Hear the Birds Singing, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Idiot's Delight, 1979 (Box 6)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1999 (Box 6)
    - In Search of ...Better Living (Box 6)
    - Invitational Festival of Experimental Theater, 1975 (Box 6)
    - J.B., 2007 (Box 6)
    - Jonesin', 2009 (Box 6)
    - Ladyhouse Blues (Box 6)
    - The Laramie Project, 2005 (Box 6)
    - The Lion and the Jewel (Box 6)
    - Lysistrata, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Macbeth, 2009 (Box 6)
    - Madmen and Specialists, 2008 (Box 6)
    - The Male Animal (Box 6)
    - Major Barbara (Box 6)
    - The Marriage of Bette and Boo, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Mary Stuart, 1982 (Box 6)
    - The Master Builder, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Measure for Measure, 2001 (Box 6)
    - The Merry Wives of Windsor (Box 6)
    - Much Ado About Nothing, 2010 (Box 6)
    - Nineteen Eighteen, 2005 (Box 6)
    - Noises Off, 2012 (Box 6)
    - Our Lady of 121st Street, 2007 (Box 6)
    - Our Town, 1993, 2010 (Box 6)
    - Pamela, 1996 (Box 6)
    - Pelleas and Melisande (Box 6)
    - Pentecost, 2010 (Box 6)
    - Playing for Time, 2007 (Box 6)
    - Pride and Prejudice, 2008 (Box 6)
    - The Relapse, 1980 (Box 6)
    - The Resurrection of Lady Lester, 1992 (Box 6)
    - Rock-n-Roll as a Metaphor for Life in America, 1996 (Box 6)
    - The Rogues' Trial (Box 6)
    - Romeo and Juliet, 1980 (Box 6)
    - She Stoops to Conquer, 2007 (Box 6)
    - Sherlock Holmes (Box 6)
    - Sirens (Box 6)
    - The Show-Off, 2009 (Box 6)
    - S'lichot (Forgiveness), 2000 (Box 6)
    - Suddenly Last Summer, 2011 (Box 6)
    - Table Manners (Box 6)
    - Tango (Box 6)
    - Tartuffe, 1981, 2009 (Box 6)
    - The Tempest, 1998, 2000 (Box 6)
    - The Time of Your Life, 1982 (Box 6)
    - To Kill a Mockingbird, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Trelawny of Wells, 1992 (Box 6)
    - Trumpets and Raspberries, 2011 (Box 6)
    - The Twelfth Night (Box 6)
    - Two by Fassbinder, 2007 (Box 6)
    - Uncommon Women and Others, 2009 (Box 6)
    - A View from the Bridge, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Wedding Band, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Wuthering Heights (Box 6)
    - You Can't Take it With You, 2006 (Box 6)
    - You Never Can Tell, 2008 (Box 6)
  - Ensemble Theater
    - BDWAY Arts (Box 7)
    - Born Yesterday (Box 7)
    - Butley (Box 7)
    - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof (Box 7)
    - Charlie the Chicken, A Resounding Tinkle, and Whiskey (Box 7)
    - Diary of a Madman (Box 7)
    - A Doll House (Box 7)
    - Mirandolina, The Blood Knot, and Wings, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Miss Julie (Box 7)
    - Old Times (Box 7)
    - The Rivals (Box 7)
  - Michigan Repertory
    - Playbills 1969-1970, 1972, 1976-1977, 1979, 1981 (Box 7)
    - The Apple Cart, 1946 (Box 7)
    - Carmen, 1947 (Box 7)
    - The King's Henchmen, 1947 (Box 7)
    - Temper the Wind, 1947 (Box 7)
  - Professional Theater Program
    - Albee Directs Albee: The American Dream and Zoo Story, Counting the Ways and Listening (Box 8)
    - As You Like It, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Ave Maris Stella (Box 8)
    - Blackstone Magic Show (Box 8)
    - Broadway (Box 8)
    - Bubbling Brown Sugar (Box 8)
    - California Suite (Box 8)
    - Chapeau and Mother Courage and Her Children (Box 8)
    - Charley's Aunt, 1976 (Box 8)
    - Claude Kipnis Mime Theater (Box 8)
    - Crimes of the Heart (Box 8)
    - The Crucible, 1985 (Box 8)
    - Da (Box 8)
    - Dancin' (Box 8)
    - Dark Solstice, 1980 (Box 8)
    - Deathtrap (Box 8)
    - Diversions and Delights (Box 8)
    - The Elephant Man (Box 8)
    - Elizabeth I (Box 8)
    - Eubie (Box 8)
    - An Evening's Frost, 1967 (Box 8)
    - The Flying Karamazov Brothers, 1984 (Box 8)
    - A French Christmas, 2 undated (Box 8)
    - Gertrude Stein (Box 8)
    - Jeeves Takes Charge (Box 8)
    - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dream Coat (Box 8)
    - A Little Night Music (Box 8)
    - Long Day's Journey into Night, 1975 (Box 8)
    - Othello (Box 8)
    - Max Morath, 1978 (Box 8)
    - Moby Dick (Box 8)
    - Morning's at Seven (Box 8)
    - Mummenschanz (Box 8)
    - My Fair Lady (Box 8)
    - Oh Coward! 1975 (Box 8)
    - The Old Vic: Macbeth and Candida (Box 8)
    - The Other Half (Box 8)
    - Pericles (Box 8)
    - She Stoops to Conquer (Box 8)
    - The Robber Bridegroom (Box 8)
    - Rogues and Vagabonds (Box 8)
    - St. Mark's Gospel (Box 8)
    - Shakespeare's People (Box 8)
    - Side by Side (Box 8)
    - Something's Afoot (Box 8)
    - The Sound of Music (Box 8)
    - Uncle Vanya (Box 8)
    - Thurber, 1977 (Box 8)
    - Wedding Band, 1966 (Box 8)
    - The White Devil (Box 8)
    - Your Arms Too Short to Box with God (Box 8)
  - University Players
    - General
      - Playbills 1960-1968, 1971-1973, undated (Box 9)
      - Antigone, 1968 (Box 9)
      - Arms and the Man, 1961 (Box 9)
      - As You Like It, 1992 (Box 9)
    - General (cont.)
      - August Snow, 1990 (Box 9)
      - The Bacchae, 1968 (Box 9)
      - Beggar on Horseback (Box 9)
      - The Broken Pitcher, 1991 (Box 9)
      - Ceremonies in Dark Old Men, 1972 (Box 9)
      - Cyrano de Bergerac, 1983 (Box 9)
      - Dark of the Moon, 1970 (Box 9)
      - The Days Between and Cassandra, 1966 (Box 9)
      - Dogg's Hamlet, Cahoot's Macbeth, 1984 (Box 9)
      - Esperanza, 1970 (Box 9)
      - The Firebugs (Box 9)
      - Five Finger Exercise, 1962 (Box 9)
      - The Girl from Maxims, 1971 (Box 9)
      - Henry IV part 1, 1961 (Box 9)
      - Henry VI, 1965 (Box 9)
      - The Hostage, 1984 (Box 9)
      - The House of Bernarda Alba, 1963 (Box 9)
      - The Inspector General (Box 9)
      - Joe Turner's Come and Gone, 1990 (Box 9)
      - Life is a Dream, 1970 (Box 9)
      - Little Mary Sunshine, 1967 (Box 9)
      - The Living Room, 1962 (Box 9)
      - London Assurance, 1984 (Box 9)
      - Long Time Since Yesterday (Box 9)
      - Lysistrata, 1969 (Box 9)
      - The Madwoman of Chailot, 1963 (Box 9)
      - The Maids and Victims of Duty, 1972 (Box 9)
      - Marat Sade, 1991 (Box 9)
      - The Merry Wives of Windsor and Henry IV, 1962 (Box 9)
      - Monique and Madame Butterfly, 1963 (Box 9)
      - Mother Courage, 1972 (Box 9)
      - The Peacemaker, 1964 (Box 9)
      - The Plough and the Stars, 1970 (Box 9)
      - Present Laughter (Box 9)
      - The Refusal (Box 9)
      - Serjeant Musgrave's Dance, 1967 (Box 9)
      - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1963 (Box 9)
      - Spell 7, 1983 (Box 9)
      - The Taming of the Shrew (Box 9)
      - Tartuffe, 1990 (Box 9)
      - The Tempest (Box 9)
      - Thieves' Carnival, 1963 (Box 9)
      - Three Sisters (Box 9)
      - The Time of Your Life, 1992 (Box 9)
      - The Trial, 1961 (Box 9)
      - Two for the Seesaw and Androcles and the Lion, 1963 (Box 9)
      - Under Milk Wood, 1962 (Box 9)
      - The White Rose, 1991 (Box 9)
    - Children's Theater
      - The Land of the Dragon, 1964 (Box 9)
      - The Plotters of Cabbage Patch Corner, 1983 (Box 9)
    - University Players Showcase
      - The Amen Corner (Box 9)
      - Antigone (Box 9)
      - The Father (Box 9)
      - The Hot L Baltimore (Box 9)
  - University Showcase
    - Blood Wedding, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Devour the Show, 1983-1984 (Box 9)
    - The Eccentricities of a Nightingale (Box 9)
    - El Hajj Malik (Box 9)
    - The First Breeze of Summer (Box 9)
    - Getting Married (Box 9)
    - In Celebration (Box 9)
    - The Lion and the Jewel (Box 9)
    - Loot (Box 9)
    - Love a la mode or Two Acts of Passion (in Fashion) (Box 9)
    - Mandragola (Box 9)
    - The Man of Mode or Sir Fopling Flutter (Box 9)
    - No Place to be Somebody (Box 9)
    - People are Living There, 1978 (Box 9)
    - The Red Lantern (Box 9)
    - Red Roses for Me (Box 9)
    - Saved, 1978 (Box 9)
    - What Every Woman Knows (Box 9)
    - When You Comin' Back, Red Ryder?, 1977 (Box 9)
- Opera Theater 1997-2012
  The Opera Theater (1.0 linear feet, 1997-2012) series contains posters from the shows of the University's opera division under the Department of Voice. Earlier opera productions are found under Department of Speech, and some are also found in the Department of Theater and Drama under the Professional Theater Program.
  - Albert Herring, 1991, 2009 undated (Box 10)
  - Armide, 2010 (Box 10)
  - The Barber of Seville, 1992 (Box 10)
  - The Bartered Bride, 2007 (Box 10)
  - The Coronation of Poppea (Box 10)
  - Cosi fan Tutte, 1977, 1995, 2006 (Box 10)
  - The Daughter of the Regiment, 2000 (Box 10)
  - Dialogues des Carmelites, 1993 (Box 10)
  - Die Fledermaus, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Don Giovanni, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Don Pasquale, 1990 (Box 10)
  - The Dreamy Kid and De Organizer, 2006 (Box 10)
  - The Elixir of Love, 2010 (Box 10)
  - Eugene Onegin, 2008 (Box 10)
  - Falstaff, 1990, 2000, 2011 undated (Box 10)
  - Hansel and Gretel (Box 10)
  - Gianni Schicchi and Il Campanello, 1996 (Box 10)
  - Jackie, 2006 (Box 10)
  - La Boheme, 1979, 1989, 2007 (Box 10)
  - La Perichole (Box 10)
  - La Serva Padrona and The Boor, 1993 (Box 10)
  - L'Elisir d'Amore (The Elixir of Love), 1996 (Box 10)
  - L'Enfant et Les Sortileges (The Child and the Enchantments) and Le Rossignol (The Nightingale) (Box 10)
  - Little Women, 2011 (Box 10)
  - The Magic Flute, 1978 (Box 10)
  - The Marriage of Figaro, 1961, 1997, 2009 (Box 10)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1995 (Box 10)
  - Old Maid and the Thief and Gianni Schicchi, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Orpheus in Hades, 1981 (Box 10)
  - Pelleas and Melisande, 1961 (Box 10)
  - The Coronation of Poppea, 2005 (Box 10)
  - Postcard from Morocco, 2008 (Box 10)
  - The Queen of Spades, 1964 (Box 10)
  - The Rake's Progress, 2012 (Box 10)
  - Susannah, 1999 (Box 10)
  - The Turn of the Screw, 2 undated (Box 10)
- Oversize Poster 1958-1991 s
  The Oversize Folders (4 oversize folders, 1958-1991) contain large format posters from the other series. Under the Department of Music heading are posters from the Symphony Band, the Carillon Bell Tower recitals, the Choir, and the Symphony and Philharmonia Orchestra. Within the Department of Theater and Drama heading are posters from the Michigan Repertory, Musket Theater, Professional Theater Program, Project Theater, University Players and University Showcase
  - Dance Company
    - Carmina Burana (Folder 1)
    - Dance Company 1978 (Folder 1)
    - Dancing on the Edge, 1991 (Folder 1)
    - Night of Fusion, 1990 (Folder 1)
    - Rite, 1976 (Folder 1)
    - University's Dancers (Folder 1)
  - Musical Theater
    - Hansel and Gretel, 1974 (Folder 1)
    - Peter Pan (Folder 1)
  - Opera Theater
    - The Abduction from the Seraglio, 1974 (Folder 1)
    - Cosi fan Tutte, 1981 (Folder 1)
    - The Crucible, 1976 (Folder 1)
    - Don Giovanni, 1975 (Folder 1)
    - Eugene Onegin, 1974 (Folder 1)
    - The Hunters, 1963 (Folder 1)
    - La Boheme, 1975 (Folder 1)
    - The Marriage of Figaro, 1973 (Folder 1)
    - Tales of Hoffman, 1975 (Folder 1)
  - Department of Speech
    - Playbill 1958, 1964 (Folder 2)
    - Invitational Festival of Experimental Theater 1974 (Folder 2)
  - Department of Music
    - Band 1976 (Folder 3)
    - Carillon 1976, 1978 (Folder 3)
    - Choir
      - Porgy and Bess (Folder 3)
    - Symphony Orchestra and Philharmonia
      - Contemporary Music Festival 1974 (Folder 3)
      - Lover and Double (Folder 3)
      - New Music for Orchestra 1976 (Folder 3)
      - Symphony No. 8 by Mahler (Folder 3)
      - University Philharmonia 1976 (Folder 3)
  - Department of Theater and Drama
    - Michigan Repertory
      - Playbills 1975, 1978 (Folder 4)
    - Musket
      - Camelot, 1976 (Folder 4)
      - Man of La Mancha (Folder 4)
      - My Fair Lady, 1971 (Folder 4)
    - Professional Theater Program
      - Camino Real (Folder 4)
      - The Consul, 1980 (Folder 4)
      - Death of a Salesman, As You Like It, Purlie, and Camino Real (Folder 4)
      - Eden, 1980 (Folder 4)
      - Equus, 1977 (Folder 4)
      - Hamlet, 1977 (Folder 4)
      - The Inspector General (Folder 4)
      - Little Theater of the Deaf (Folder 4)
      - Richard II, 1978 (Folder 4)
      - The River Niger, 1979 (Folder 4)
      - Secret Honor (Folder 4)
      - Shakespeare's People (Folder 4)
      - Spring Awakening, 1980 (Folder 4)
      - Under Milk Wood, 1978 (Folder 4)
    - Project Theater
      - Every Good Boy Deserves Favor (Folder 4)
      - Oedipus (Folder 4)
      - Waiting for Godot (Folder 4)
    - University Players
      - Playbill 1961-1964, 1968-1969, 1973-1974, undated (Folder 4)
    - University Showcase
      - Dear Antoine, 1978 (Folder 4)
      - End of Summer (Folder 4)